Prologue: Christina’s Recollections

In her youth, Christina Beltrum considered herself to be someone special.

She was born as the first princess of Beltrum, first in line to succeed the throne of the most influential kingdom of the Strahl region, blessed with both academic and magic talent, and hailed as a genius by all her instructors in everything she learned.

Hard work wasn’t difficult for her, either. She considered working hard to be a natural obligation imposed upon her because of who she was—a person that stood above others. Plus, if she worked hard to get better results, her parents would praise her, and her beloved little sister would look up to her with respect.

That’s why she was naturally able to work harder than the average person from as early as the age of three or four. She wanted to meet her parents’ expectations. She wanted to be an older sister worth respecting.

Her hard work paid off. She never experienced failure and was hailed as a genius no matter what she did. It was truly smooth sailing throughout her entire youth.

However, that background caused her belief that she was a superior, special person that stood above others to gradually grow stronger. Because she was special, there was nothing she couldn’t do. There was no one above her. Her pride grew until it was all she could believe.

And yet, despite that, she never considered her less-talented little sister to be stupid. She adored Flora. She was also happy to be complimented by her parents. As royalty, there were few people that could treat her on an equal level, so she always treasured her family.

Which was why when she was seven years old, her world fell apart when she learned that Flora had been kidnapped on her ceremonial outing outside of the castle. She followed Vanessa and Celia, who had gone to investigate on the confidential order of her father; she forcibly snuck out of the castle in what was a most foolish act.

She arrived in the slums of the capital. It was her first time stepping into such a place—a place she normally would have never ventured in her lifetime.

There, she met an orphan.

His name was Rio.

His messy hair was long enough to cover his face, his skin was rough and covered in dirt and grime, and his tattered clothes had a sour stench to them. On top of that, the boy himself was withering away.

He was the same age as Christina, and lived a life that was completely opposite from the one she spent in the castle as royalty.

So there are children like this in the world—that was what she thought after seeing an orphan for the first time in her life. But she didn’t know how to approach such a boy, and—with her rising panic over Flora’s kidnapping—ended up hurtling inexcusable words at him.

Rio’s response was unexpectedly polite. They weren’t able to gain any beneficial information from their first conversation with him, but later, they spotted Rio carrying an unconscious Flora through the slums. Christina flew into a rage—this orphan had lied to her face, saying he knew nothing about her sister.

Christina slapped Rio and screamed at him, but Rio stared back at her with a gaze that chilled her to her core. It scared her into reflexively attempting to slap him again, but Rio caught her hand. When she tried to slap him with her free hand, he caught the other one, too.

And that...

That was the first time she had ever had her freedom taken away from her by force.

That was the first time she had ever been glared at coldly.

That was the first time she had ever thought of another human as terrifying.

Because she was the first princess, no one had ever treated her rudely or roughly. Everyone had always respected her.

She was mortified. Her pride had been wounded. She realized that she wasn’t actually a special person at all, but rather, an extremely unreliable girl.

Christina had been fiercely enraged at the time, but looking back on it now, the events of that day were probably what made her come to the realization that she wasn’t someone special. She was a normal person no different from anyone else.

She was simply born in the position of the first princess. What was special was her position, not herself. That became even more clear once she started attending the Royal Academy.

Indeed, she was able to produce results better than the average person in every field. But her talents stopped there. She was able to maintain her top scores in the academy, but that was simply because she was well-behaved and studied hard.

She didn’t have any prodigy-like talent, and couldn’t compete with the true geniuses of each field. For example, Celia Claire was considered a genius sorcerer—and Christina was no match for her. She had once read the thesis Celia submitted to skip her grades and though she could understand its contents, she couldn’t imagine writing something similar at the age Celia had been.

Besides...

There was one more person that could have been a genius. She didn’t want to accept it at first, but that person was Rio.

He couldn’t have had a proper education in the slums, yet he was able to read and write shortly after entering the academy, eventually pulling ahead of the rest of the students to reach the same top grades as Christina. He had tremendous learning capability.

Christina had prided herself on her ability to study, so she had been secretly shocked at the time. If she were in Rio’s position, would she be able to achieve the same grades as him?

On top of that, she saw him practicing with his sword after class multiple times. His form was extremely beautiful—his movements were clearly different from the other students.

He was elegant, yet sharp, with movements honed until he stood far above anyone else in terms of skill level. Perhaps that was why Christina found herself captivated by the sight of him swinging his sword before she realized it.

Yes, he must be a genius, she thought.

But that realization didn’t change the relationship between them, and she continued to do her best to avoid him on the academy grounds. Part of the reason why was because of the guilt and awkwardness she felt about their first meeting. Even if she were to reach out to him, she didn’t know what to say. Because of what had happened, she didn’t think he wanted to talk to her, either.

More importantly, she was the first princess. She couldn’t just thoughtlessly apologize to other people, as it could end up causing a bigger problem.

She was special, but it was a restrictive kind of special.

Considering the inconvenience she could cause for her father, who was already distracted by the power struggles within the country, she decided to refrain from any actions that could cause discord.

Being born into a special position meant that she had to act like someone extraordinary. Even if it wasn’t true...

That was the duty of someone like her—of royalty entrusted with the rule of a kingdom, she believed.

However, when she saw Rio isolated in the academy, she felt a sense of discomfort she couldn’t identify.

The sons of nobility mistakenly assumed themselves to be special and acted with no consideration for others. Watching them reminded Christina of her past self, causing feelings of shame to well up alongside the discomfort within her.

When she saw Flora’s sad face on top of all that, she felt pathetic. Powerless to do anything against this reality...

Yet, despite that, she maintained her path as a spectator.

And the result of that was a scapegoat being born. Rio must have sensed the danger he was in, as he disappeared without a trace and never appeared before Christina again.

The memories, as sour as they were, sometimes resurfaced on a whim.

They would never meet again. Rio would be better off that way.

With that thought in mind, she nailed the coffin shut over her bitter memories.

That is, until today...

Bonus Short Stories

One Particular Morning

Early one morning, at a time when most people would normally be asleep...

“Good morning, Onii-chan.”

Rio woke up to Latifa clinging onto him from above.

“Good morning... Is it already time to get up?” Rio asked sleepily with a slight yawn.

“Nope! It’s still a little early, but...” Latifa shook her head nervously. She looked like she wanted to say something, which Rio found to be a little strange.

“Is something the matter?” he asked.

“Promise you won’t laugh?”

“I’m afraid I can’t do that until I hear what it is...”

Latifa pouted. “Mmrgh... Promise you won’t laugh!” she insisted. It seemed she wasn’t going to answer until he agreed.

Rio folded to her demands and nodded. “All right. I won’t laugh.”

“I had a scary dream, so I didn’t want to be awake by myself...”

Which was why she woke Rio up. Latifa looked a little embarrassed as she explained herself.

“I see...” Rio chuckled.

“Ah, you laughed!” Latifa whined unhappily.

“I’m not laughing,” Rio denied, petting Latifa’s head as it rested on his chest.

“Hmph...” Latifa puffed up her cheeks in objection, but she didn’t resist the head pats from her beloved adopted brother, obediently surrendering herself to him.

“What kind of dream was it?” Rio asked as he continued to pet her head.

“It was a dream about the past. We were traveling together, but you suddenly disappeared.”

“Don’t worry--I’m right here.”

“Yeah...” Latifa’s reply was a little uneasy. She tightened her grip around Rio.

“Would you like to sleep together?” Rio looked up and asked.

“Yeah.” The reply this time was much more assured.

“Then you should get off me first. Sleeping like this will make you catch a cold.”

“Okay!” Latifa obeyed and happily relocated next to him.

“Here, come under the blankets.”

“Okay!” Latifa immediately crawled into the bed and snuggled up to Rio, beaming with happiness. “Ehehe--it’s warm. And it smells like you. So cozy.”

“Let’s go to sleep, then.” Since he’d been roused at such an early hour, his body was still yearning for sleep. Rio yawned once again.

“Yup. Good night, Onii-chan,” Latifa replied obediently, hugging Rio’s side and closing her eyes.

“Good night,” Rio said gently.

It seemed Latifa was still sleepy herself, as she fell asleep in no time at all.

She must’ve forgotten about the dream already.

Relieved by the sight of Latifa’s peaceful sleeping face, Rio also let himself drift off. Less than a minute later, the two of them were both sleeping soundly.

However, when Rio woke up an hour later and tried to get them both up...

“Nooo, I want to sleep with Onii-chan more!”

Latifa’s insistent clinging and refusal to release Rio resulted in the two of them settling down for their third round of sleep.

A New Way of Calling

It happened on the way from Cleia to Rodania, while they were preparing lunch in a clearing off the road.

“Celia.”

Certain circumstances had led to Rio addressing Celia without a title. There had been an awkward bashfulness at first, but he was gradually growing used to it after continuously doing so over the span of a few days.

“Yes, Haruto?” Celia was now completely used to it, as she showed no embarrassment in her reaction.

“Could you produce some water with magic for me?”

“Sure, I can do that.”

Rio summoned Celia over to the food preparation bench and had her prepare some water.

“We’ve been walking for consecutive days now. How are you holding up?” Rio asked while she filled a pot with water.

“I’m fine. It’d be a lie if I said I wasn’t tired, but I’m not in any pain. I’ve never had the chance to travel so much on foot before, so I’m actually finding it pretty fun,” Celia replied with a giggle.

“Is that so?”

“What about you, Haruto? Are you tired? I know it’s not every day, but you’ve been carrying us as you run every three days.”

“It’s not that big of a deal. I’m also finding it fun traveling with you, Celia,” Rio said with a soft smile.

“R-Really, now...?” A faint pink tinted Celia’s cheeks.

“Thankfully, our trip has been going smoothly. Let’s pray that nothing happens before we reach Rodania.”

“It’s a little saddening to have the journey come to and end, but... You’re right.” Celia nodded, a faraway look in her eyes.

“Speaking of which, once we part ways with Her Highness and return to our regular lives, should I go back to calling you what I used to?” Rio asked.

“Well... No, it’s okay. You can keep doing what you’re doing now. It’d get too confusing otherwise.”

She finally got him to call her by her name... was the reason Celia didn’t voice out loud, and her cheeks reddened once more.

Hiroaki smiled in satisfaction, turning back to Duke Huguenot. “...So, out of the leading nobles in the Galarc Kingdom, which houses have currently sent proposals?”

“The major ones are the Galarc Kingdom’s third princess, Princess Rosalie, and Duke Gregory’s Lady Lisette, I believe,” answered Duke Huguenot. Liselotte’s name was not mentioned.

“Lisette aside, Rosalie was only twelve or thirteen, right? Ah, but I guess that’s right at the start of the expected marriage age in this world.”

Hiroaki recalled the girl named Rosalie he met at a tea party not long ago. For the record, she was also Charlotte’s little sister.

“Indeed so.”

“Hmm, I see... Anyone else?” Hiroaki asked.

“In terms of prominent ones, those two are far ahead of the others. The family status of the other ladies are a little lower in comparison.”

“Hmm...” Hiroaki hummed vaguely.

So there was no proposal from Liselotte, huh? Even if Flora was my first wife, Liselotte would definitely make it to the second or third seat. But I guess she’s busy—she left right after the banquet to go to work, after all.

It was still possible for a proposal from Liselotte to drop in at any time, but he still found it a little disappointing that there was no proposal from her right now.

“Will we be remaining in Galarc for much longer?”

“There are still several events to attend, but once they’re done, we should be able to return to Rodania.”

“Right... Ah, then let’s slowly make our way back to Rodania once they’re over. I’d also like to drop by Liselotte’s place on our way back—I didn’t get to say farewell to her properly at the banquet.”

If she wouldn’t show herself readily, then he’d just have to go to her. Honest to his desires, Hiroaki suggested they return just so he could meet Liselotte. That fact was probably seen through easily by Duke Huguenot and the sharp-minded Roanna beside him.

That being said, Duke Huguenot would gladly welcome a marriage between Hiroaki and Liselotte. Honestly, Liselotte’s marriage alone would overwhelmingly outweigh marrying both Rosalie and Lisette in terms of benefits.

“Understood,” Duke Huguenot chuckled with a smile, bowing his head respectfully.

Epilogue: Yearning to be Special

There was no use crying over spilt milk.

In the near future, every force in the lands would become frantic to win over Haruto Amakawa.

This wasn’t a hunch.

It wasn’t a belief, either—

It was a prophecy.

He was special.

He was one like no other.

Special, and worthy of standing above all others.

In reality, an army of five thousand had fallen helplessly before him.

And yet...

How foolish.

He had once stood below everyone else.

They were the ones who had once placed him there.

Fierce regret surged forth.

Intense guilt welled up.

Violent rage formed from regret.

And above all the regret, guilt, and rage...

Was a strong sense of admiration and curiosity.

It piqued countless times across this journey and subsided every time...

It was a burning sense of yearning.

What if...

What if he had been born of Beltrum royalty instead? The Beltrum Kingdom would have surely ended up different from the way it was now.

What if... What if he lent his power to them...?

She started hallucinating such possibilities.

Because she only possessed a fake kind of “special.”

She clung to it...

All the while yearning for something genuine.

What if, what if...? she wondered.

The genuine kind of “special” was dazzling.

She was powerless—it was pathetic.

And yet, that genuine power shone so brightly...

But such “what-if”s did not exist.

Because she was calm...

Because she berated herself in an effort to be calmer than anyone else...

She was quick to return to her senses.

It was why the intense guilt and regret returned quickly, too.

It told her that she was too late to change anything now.

Strangely enough, there was no rage.

Even if there was to be conflict over Haruto Amakawa, they would never be allowed to join in.

That was the penalty their kingdom had to pay for the crimes they committed.

That’s why this yearning...

It had to be sealed away after all.

As she watched Rio walk towards her, dragging Charles by the scruff of his neck...

Christina Beltrum berated herself in a calmer manner than anyone else.